<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.nzbdav"
       name="NZB-DAV"
       version="0.6.12"
       provider-name="nzbdav">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Stream Usenet media through TMDBHelper</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Stream Usenet media through TMDBHelper</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Browse movies and TV shows in TMDBHelper, pick a source from Usenet, and stream it directly in Kodi. NZB-DAV searches your NZBHydra2 indexers, downloads through nzbdav, and plays the file over WebDAV — no manual NZB handling required. Includes smart quality filtering, on-the-fly MP4 to MKV remuxing with subtitle support, and full seeking with a progress bar.</description>
        <description lang="en">Browse movies and TV shows in TMDBHelper, pick a source from Usenet, and stream it directly in Kodi. NZB-DAV searches your NZBHydra2 indexers, downloads through nzbdav, and plays the file over WebDAV — no manual NZB handling required. Includes smart quality filtering, on-the-fly MP4 to MKV remuxing with subtitle support, and full seeking with a progress bar.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Requires your own NZBHydra2 and nzbdav instances plus valid API/WebDAV access. No content is provided.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Requires your own NZBHydra2 and nzbdav instances plus valid API/WebDAV access. No content is provided.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/xbmc4lyfe/nzbdavkodi</source>
        <website>https://xbmc4lyfe.github.io/nzbdavkodi/</website>
        <news>v0.6.11
- Preserve full modal error dialog text where Kodi's Dialog API allows it
- Show NZBHydra outages and invalid responses in modal dialogs
- Keep duplicate NZB results visible instead of merging indexers

v0.6.10
- Show modal error dialog on every playback failure (replaces toast notifications)
- Detect post-resolve stream crashes (missing articles, auth rejection) with error dialog
- Clear playlist on stream failure to prevent TMDBHelper retry loop

v0.6.9
- Deduplicate identical NZBs from multiple indexers (same title+size), show "Multiple" as indexer
- Send configured max results limit to NZBHydra2 API (was hardcoded to 100)

v0.6.8
- Fix playback failing due to URL-encoded '=' in auth header (Kodi pipe syntax)
- Show download failures in a modal dialog instead of a toast notification
- Clear video playlist on resolve failure to prevent Kodi retry loop

v0.6.7
- Fix pylint W0621: remove redundant import os in _serve_temp_faststart

v0.6.6
- Validate URL scheme in stream proxy to reject non-HTTP URLs
- Redact API keys and auth credentials from debug logs
- Reuse shared notification helper (remove duplicated logic)
- Reduce _serve_remux complexity by extracting seek and faststart helpers
- Localize "no video file found" notification string
- Truncate server failure messages to 80 chars for TV UI
- Fix all code scanning alerts (complexity, indentation, broad-except)

v0.6.5
- Show nzbdav failure reason to user when download fails
- Notify user when download completes but no video file found on WebDAV
- Show stream errors to user instead of silently swallowing them
- Fix playback freeze caused by ffmpeg stderr pipe buffer filling up

v0.6.2
- Fix flaky cache eviction test due to non-deterministic file sizes

v0.6.1
- Fix remaining code scanning alerts (broad-except, locally-disabled)

v0.6.0
- Fix all code scanning alerts (complexity, broad-except, continuation)
- Fix pylint warnings (nesting, unused import, consider-using-in)

v0.5.0
- Simplify settings: TMDBHelper-only install, remove WebDAV URL field
- Release group multiselect dialogs with curated defaults
- Fix continuation requests restarting ffmpeg from byte 0

v0.4.3
- Remux MP4 to MKV on the fly via ffmpeg (fixes 32-bit Kodi CFileCache bug)
- Subtitle conversion (mov_text to SRT) with toggleable setting
- Byte-range seeking with duration probe and progress bar
- Background service for stream proxy and playback auto-recovery
- Fix playback-failed dialog caused by setResolvedUrl

v0.4.1
- Address high/medium findings from code review

v0.4.0
- Show lightning bolt indicator for already-downloaded NZBs
- Suppress BrokenPipeError log spam when stopping playback

v0.3.0
- WebDAV streaming on CoreELEC with MP4 faststart proxy
- Skip re-downloading if NZB already completed in nzbdav history
- Test Connection buttons for NZBHydra and nzbdav in settings
- Retry NZB submission up to 3 times on transient failure
- Show filter count and offer to show all when everything filtered
- LRU cache eviction when cache exceeds 50MB limit
- Use IMDB ID for TV show searches

v0.2.0
- Kodi localization support for addon UI and settings labels
- Repository best-practice metadata and coverage tests

v0.1.0
- Initial release with NZBHydra2 search, nzbdav streaming, TMDBHelper integration
- PTT-based quality filtering, custom results dialog, search caching</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
